# **INTERNSHIP RESUME**



# Fatyn Nurraihanah binti Seman

Bandar Tun Hussein Onn, Cheras, 43200, Selangor

### **OBJECTIVE**

I am a highly determined Information Technology student with varied academic knowledge paired with a passion for learning. I am extremely adaptable and flexible to learn and adjust to new circumstances and scenarios. I am also trained with good soft skills and have a dedication to gain new experiences

### LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

**MALAY** 

**ENGLISH** 

### **EDUCATION**

### SEPT 2018 - PRESENT

Universiti Teknologi Petronas

**Bachelor of Information Technology** CGPA: 3.65

#### **JULY 2017 - JUNE 2018**

Universiti Teknologi Petronas

Foundation of Technology in Information and Communication Technology CGPA: 3.49

#### 2012 - 2016

MRSM Alor Gajah

### **PROFESSIONAL**

HTML VISUAL BASIC **CSS** ADOBE INDESIGN

JAVA ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

PHP **JAVASCRIPT** 

**XML** ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

C++ **PHYTON PASCAL** SOL

R MICROSOFT OFFICE

### **INTERNSHIP PERIOD: JUNE 2020 - DEC 2020**

### COLLEGE EXTRACURRICULAR INVOLVEMENT

#### MEDIA AND DESIGN MANAGER FOR **DEVELOPER STUDENT CLUB UTP**

SEPT 2019 - PRESENT

Co-founded Developer Student Club branch in UTP, a university program by Google Developers

#### **HEAD OF DEPARTMENT FOR**

SPONSORSHIP AND PUBLIC RELATION SEPT 2019 - MARCH 2020 FOR COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT PROJECT

A project that was conducted under University Social Responsibility program aiming to improve the well-being of community

#### **EXECUTIVE OF IT AND DESIGN FOR** CORPORATE CAREER EXPOSURE JUNE 2019 - NOV 2019

An event that acts as a platform for graduates and students to engage with employers and to seek for employments, internship and possible opportunities

#### **COMMITTEE OF BUSINESS AND**

FUNDING FOR RECONSA

OCT 2018 - JUNE 2019

An event that acts as a platform for our students and international students to participate in activities and presentations on global issues and matters

#### FACILITATOR FOR TRAIN OF TRAINEES 2 OCT 2019 - 7 OCT 2019

A program that was conducted by a group of students to teach and give exposure to juniors about robotic and Arduino

### PARTICIPATOR FOR ROBOTIC

COMPETITION

8 MAY 2018 - 12 JULY 2018

Group of selected students representing UTP to compete in a Robotic Competition which we undergo the training, building and coding of the robot. We achieve to stand till the quarter final of the competition

### **CORE SUBJECTS**

- Structure Programming
- Computer System
- System Analysis and Design
- Statistics and Empirical Method
- **Data and Information Management**
- **Network Management**
- **Object Oriented Programming**
- Discrete Mathematics
- Data Communication and Network
- Web Application and Intergrative programming
- Wireless Technology
- **Human and Computer Interaction**
- Introduction to Data Science
- IT Professional and Ethics

### **INTEREST**

- Software analysis/design
- UI/UX design
- Data science
- Telecommunication networking
- Programming

### RECOGNITION AND AWARD

#### Dean's List Award

Obtained Dean's List Award for every past semester during Undergraduate study

#### 1st Runner Up for Oh My Coding Competition

A group program coding competition using Visual Basic that is done during our foundation studies which I led

### OTHER SKILLS

- Photography
- Videography
- Graphic Design

### MINOR SUBJECTS

- Health, Safety and Environment
- Entrepreneurship
- Academic Writing
- Thinking Skills
- Business Management
- Principle of Economics
- Scientific Inquiry
- Professional Communication Skills
- Minoring in Corporate Management
  - Principles of Marketing

### PROJECT EXPERIENCE

#### GAME STORE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM MAY 2019 - NOV 2019

A group project that was done using SQL language to store database and show the relations between entities and its attribute for Data and Information Management subject

#### PRINTING STORE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM SEPT 2018 - NOV 2018

A group project that was done using C++ language. This project was done to help the printing store we interviewed. We build the system based on their requirements and demand. The project was for Structured Programming and System Analysis and Design subject

# APPLICATION FOR DOWN SYNDROME PEOPLE

MARCH 2018 - MAY 2018

A group project that was done using Visual Basic language to assist or be used by underprivileged. Our group specifically chosen down syndrome people after number of research and reference. We created an application that would help them study some basic knowledge at their early ages. The project was for Fundamental of Programming subject

### **REFERENCES**

#### Dr Rohiza binti Ahmad

Computer & Information Sciences Department, Senior Lecturer, Universiti Teknologi Petronas +6(05)-3687477 +6(019)-4640913 rohiza\_ahmad@utp.edu.my

### Dr. Mohamed Nordin Zakaria

Computer & Information Science Department, Senior Lecturer, Universiti Teknologi Petronas +6(05)-3687494/ 8209 +6(012)-2761336 nordinzakaria@utp.edu.my